[
	{
		"question_num": 1,
		"question" : "How do you print Hello World in Java?", 
		"answers" : [
					"print(\"Hello World\")", 
					"System.out.println(\"Hello World\");", 
					"System.out.println(\"Hello World\")",
					"print(\"Hello World\");"
					], 
		"correct_answer" : 2
	}, 
	{
		"question_num": 2, 
		"question" : "How do you print Hello World in C?", 
		"answers" : [
			"print(\"Hello World\")", 
			"System.out.println(\"Hello World\");", 
			"printf(\"Hello World\");",
			"std::cout << \"Hello World\" << std::endl;"
		], 
		"correct_answer" : 3
	}, 
	{
		"question_num": 3, 
		"question" : "How do you print Hello World in C++?", 
		"answers" : [
			"print(\"Hello World\")", 
			"System.out.println(\"Hello World\");", 
			"printf(\"Hello World\");",
			"cout << \"Hello World\";"
		], 
		"correct_answer" : 4
	}, 
	{
		"question_num": 4, 
		"question" : "How do you print Hello World in Python?", 
		"answers" : [
			"print(\"Hello World\")", 
			"System.out.println(\"Hello World\");", 
			"printf(\"Hello World\");",
			"cout << \"Hello World\";"
		], 
		"correct_answer" : 1
	},
	{
		"question_num": 5,
		"question": "How do you read a string from user input in Java?",
		"answers": [
			"scanf(\"%s\", str);",
			"String str = input();",
			"String str = scanner.nextLine();",
			"getline(cin, str);"
		],
		"correct_answer": 3
	},
	{
		"question_num": 6,
		"question": "How do you read a string from user input in C?",
		"answers": [
			"String str = input();",
			"scanf(\"%s\", str);",
			"cin >> str;",
			"input_string = input()"
		],
		"correct_answer": 2
	},
	{
		"question_num": 7,
		"question": "How do you read a string from user input in C++?",
		"answers": [
			"getline(cin, str);",
			"String str = scanner.nextLine();",
			"scanf(\"%s\", str);",
			"input_string = input()"
		],
		"correct_answer": 1
	},
	{
		"question_num": 8,
		"question": "How do you read a string from user input in Python?",
		"answers": [
			"scanf(\"%s\", str);",
			"cin >> str;",
			"input_string = input()",
			"String str = scanner.nextLine();"
		],
		"correct_answer": 3
	},
	{
		"question_num": 9,
		"question": "How do you declare an integer variable with value 42 in Java?",
		"answers": [
			"int num = 42;",
			"num = 42",
			"integer num = 42;",
			"int num := 42;"
		],
		"correct_answer": 1
	},
	{
		"question_num": 10,
		"question": "How do you declare an integer variable with value 42 in C?",
		"answers": [
			"num = 42;",
			"int num = 42;",
			"integer num = 42;",
			"int num := 42;"
		],
		"correct_answer": 2
	},
	{
		"question_num": 11,
		"question": "How do you declare an integer variable with value 42 in C++?",
		"answers": [
			"num = 42;",
			"int num = 42;",
			"integer num = 42;",
			"int num := 42;"
		],
		"correct_answer": 2
	},
	{
		"question_num": 12,
		"question": "How do you declare an integer variable with value 42 in Python?",
		"answers": [
			"int num = 42;",
			"num = 42",
			"integer num = 42;",
			"int num := 42;"
		],
		"correct_answer": 2
	}
]
